I know, we called it over the regress guilty of meeting my city council.
Monday May 1st 2023 2 Mr Theo to Bless Parker?
Excuse me...
Excuse me....
What's your father...?
Your son is wherever you are!
Then i will support a bay and have been in constitution at United States
And then post-cution at the State of Oklahoma.
and then I will not directly receive the rest of your interest.
Not only, we see correctly or indirectly
any many are other valuable things
for the performance
or no performance of any actor duty.
For the performance, for not performing to be accurate duty
for Canadians who write office other than that purpose
and a lot by law
for taking into account the office
as an compensation allowed
I'd rather just wear our clothes
but i'm from this where ever
then will date with these charge
you know thankfully, they're fairly discharged
according
According
the duties of my office
very such time as I serve as a mayor
and to city of Miami
for access times that served with Mayor
to your mayor
and to your mayor
especially
as you see in Miami
for three
proclamation declaring May 1st 2023
is anti-violence day
Hi
hi
I'm sorry
this was asked for by the pop-all tribe
so we will get that presented in
4 public improvements
We have nine
five
six
minutes from April 17th and
April 24th
the 70s
Regor meeting 24
Special Meeting
March 2nd
Budget Amendment
Number 23
The chair is to purchase
Bucker here
and CBB receding
and
the 25,000
out of a county
Our program for
Marking
2 separate
So there is
just in case
There
The
the
CBB is a grant from
the county's
Marking
and that does not match
So
The
the money
is actually housed
Thank you, Joe.
I'm very let our support from the city of Mayan for
The Department and Commerce Emergency Solutions grant
to Community Crisis Center as well
as I know she has a fill in here
No no not healthy yes
Stephanie Cromwell thank
You
Um i am hearing
From community crisis center we come every year
As
We have been last about 22 years
To ask
For
Our Emergency Shelter grant
Which we received through HUD
And it helps to pay for the operational cost
and expenses out at our shelter
It's been very important
Each year,
We see more
More people in
The past Year
20% increase
In
Number of victims
And their children
That were requesting needed shelter
Instead of you guys serve
3 county here
We do Craig Delaware in Ottawa
4 offices
Thib
Venetia Grove
Jay
Miami
and then our shelter location
Under Billman New Office
In my have a correct
Yes we are
You had the capital campaign going now
Check it out
To build over on B Street
Which would double the size of our
Headquarters
And allow us to provide a lot more
Non-residential services
The sort
To try and decide
On that side
I understand you guys very excited about
That because
i've been in your facility
It's pretty
Pretty
At course
Our building is old
Following apart
So it will be
Very nice
This
Is
Support
Our shelter
And we are lucky to have you guys
In the community
Kelsey is a rock star
Actually
We're lucky
Have her run in
The operation
So I'm making motion
We approve
This support
Take it
Worker
William
Hi
Thank You
Thanks, Deputy
I am 9
Don't Resolution
MSUA
2023-252023
It counts as
A.M.,
And the Board of Trustees
For MSUA
Authorizing
Communities
Financial Support
The P-Wayers
To the frozen outfit
On Development
At 329
So
Motion to approve
Second
Hi
William
Congratulations
You bet
All right
Anything else from us?
Let's know
Keep going
Absolutely
Thanks guys
Our GAR Submaterial British Fliers
Maintenance Service Contract
Number
C23-13
With Anne's Flower and Guess
For fiscal year
Good job
We got here
Are
Some Terry
British maintenance service contract
And we've
Got 15
Graved out there
Some Jerry
British Cadets
The regers
The pilot is being trained
In the past
I'm not
This
Is just a contract for
Maintenances of those grapes
I'll make a motion to approve
Second
Hi
Is that
William Sky
Parker
Thanks
Welcome
Remember
Of understanding
Between the city of MIMA and
The youth athletic
Development Foundation for use
A little leaves
Baseball complex
In
P-Way fields
At Francis Morgan Field
For 2223C
And
Greeting
Again
This is our annual
New York Youth
We have a little bit of
There is one
Change that our
Director
Attention
To
And That would be
Number
Three
3-V
Agreement
Basically what this
Is
Lowing
For these organizations
They
Have exclusive rights
In their
Remail year time
During the season
The reason why we brought to
Something about
One
Of
This
We had several
Dulk's
Out there playing soccer
Not allowing our kids to practice
During their practices a lot of time
Our complexes are considered
A park right now
So it basically
Like
Three access
This gives those organizations
The ability
To
All PD
And
Say
we have an agreement
It be here
You guys do not
They don't really have any teeth
We do that in the past
So this gives them a lot of
Teeth
This is basically
Really
You know what changed
Who's it?
Was
That big an issue
It was
A nightly
I got calls all time
During
The fall
Now we haven't
Remained to
That so far
Just here but
Unfortunately
Kids are missing practices
And during
Because adults were
Out there
Is
The PD ever called on
Um
I think they have
About no
For sure
We need to
Be
And this gives us all the teeth
That we never
So
This is what
What
Our kids can use it
Over
The adults
They're not
Not
They don't know
Right
Absolutely
I
You got
You guys
Believe
If you had
through the lead, this currently is used in that.
They don't need to be out there during their a lot of time overseas
This really doesn' have an opportunity for them all you
but how does it feel coming up here?
It's come along pretty good!
Come on and get...
We've soon seen some of those
who are paralyzed from around last week
because we needed at Badway
But I'm excited about
that the NEOSA board is really excited about
and next couple years, one of those things
to start taking a shake.
They look...
You drive out there now
you can tell
how different it's in our green
And if we're close they are compared
with once every opponent
who will fall
for around 2 days or so
but today I got an email from
not soccer boards
which have pledged
$500 worth of pool seat
and grassy
due goes towards their next project
It looks cool!
Motion to approve?
Second
Number 12
BMOU
Member of the State
and I'm going to go on a soccer association
at Samwell's Soc Crown Flex for 2223C
The exact same thing
Motion
Third
Second
The agreement that we have
been working on to allow
entities
To help us out in the concession
and also
poocharchs
become two
or
tournaments
We hope
but it's all about
whatever
An accession side of things
is getting tougher
than these days
to find people worth
So this kind
helps
to come
to see
the spawner
as they can
come into
health
and the past
portion
So
we get to
constantly
I can't
about food trucks
allowing them
to come out of our
supplements for example
You like what's one
Of
And this
This is a building
offer that
To
Where
The conditions
you have any particular
Anity in mind
Just open it up
In
the
year
We took over
you're anybody any body's parent,
instead they want to take it over.
So one thing I told Kevin
and my come on board
we were starting see the trend of parents
with just not getting involved in
what are these two big
or needs for organizations
And i can't sit back
when this is watch that go under
so everyone taken a long
um...
This year
My high school softball
research clubs
going help us
assess things during direct weeks
well overseas
all process
planning
schedule
all the gains
but got
43 teams
in the league, right around to say it's sort of a 130-to 450 girls point.
So we'll incur all that revenue from signups and things like
That they might help set access stand
It's not exposed here there is nothing I'm ever year deal
But your approach at nearly 20 places where even
The part or ban you have to go see some places
Staffing has their own, as well
We had this happening people tackle
We run with it but this year's been a struggle
I'm trying to find, we might have at least 30 people in that event staff
But my get two of them said they can work
So...I should point out on
This years agreement
Because the time constraints
That were looking yet
There is an agreement he was talking about
Make sure you need open up for everybody
To be able
The ability
You just say, remember legal I guess you're going to bring those
This is them
Okay so we are actually both on
I think it's not correct
And this will allow y the FF
Middle East baseball and my house basketball tournaments
Just goes right back into their years program
The part of that
Whatever would get us from our back
Biggest partnership
I just got up on the day with the lay inputs
On three with 3 soccer tournaments
A chance to get them about this
But so, a couple of months ago
June and we'll host at 33 tournament
To bring him 40 50 teams
Any other essay can run those concessions
We will be able
And things like that for my revenue standpoint
What do you say?
They won't give portions as well
So only food truck park
You need to do that at all
The sports complex has needed
They're reading here still
Take a second, tell you
Your doing the great job of seeing different groups
Of people who are bringing into their community
A softball tournament was last weekend
And when not to go she is there's line
When chapters or lines of people
So in fact
That your making with the infrastructure
The main thing is great for our small businesses
This time so
Kudos to you
For the infrastructure put in
Because paying off
So appreciate it
It's a group effort
It has been huge
I have no idea about that
But, yeah
A lot of hours
With changing people
I think about the first time
We're going to go for a second
Hi
Thank you
14 or 23, 2023
That's 0.4
Mending chapter 3
The code of ordinances
It is entirely providing severability
Providing for conflicting provisions
So this was discussed
The work session
And rather than as continuously
Emitting our alcohol
Ordnance to match whatever changes
Legislature makes with the state law
This just incorporates
To set for specific provisions that are listed here
So, For instance
In section 3-3 dash
4O
The reason for that is
the state law
Requires
That's a mayor sign everything
But it gives
It allows somebody else to sign
And so we've just taken this
State Law
Change different mayors
To manage your orders
As you can see
The state law is not that
Pretty much matches the State Law
We took care of
Legalities
Instead, instead it's in on and unlike
That
And there are two changes from what you were provided
In your original packet
With yorkiational tax
And you can see the parameters of how
You wanted that assess which we did
But there was lingering questions in my mind
Because
The state statute states
There are only certain kinds
Of licenses
That this city could charge a
Occupational tax for
Looking at what other cities have done
They've listed an occupational
Tax from many other
So the general counsel of
The Abel Commission and I've been playing
Telephone tag for quite some time
But we actually talked today
And he agreed with my concern
That state statute
List specific licenses that you can do it
For, which means
You cannot do everything
It's not on this list
The other thing that can happen
Of course, is the legislature
Can very easily go in and modify
This state statute
And it's not on this list
But we're going to be charging an occupational tax
For some things
That are never in cities do
As general counsel said
None of them have been tested
But they can very easily go in and modify the statute
And I would recommend
To my friend that's sitting there now
That, They need to do
In a law us have an occupational tax
For everything
The Abel has license for
Until it happens
At least its opinion of general counsel
For Able
As My opinion
We cannot
Do the Occupational Tax
The other change to the ordinance from what you are originally given
Is we're going have this ordinance go into effect
In 30 days
Uh,
Problem with that is
That means it would mean
Ornits goes in affect
Basically on June 1
It's an annual occupational tax
That's based on the fiscal year
that would mean everybody
Would owe The Tax as of June 1
And then Everybody will know
As a July one
I thought
A new you all well enough to
You wouldn't want back
To happen
So we're ending
Effective date
If don' t, i can without it change
Basically the occupational tax is set at half
What of what The State allows
But not less than $200
Or maximum amount
That this state law allows if it's under
Hey that sounds pretty good
I think a brilliant person thought
Thank you
You're welcome
Hang on
Hi tower
We're having a discussion on that tomorrow
But it's my understanding
That is collected through the utility
Okay
So what happens to
I'll pay like they haven't been back
Then we let Abel Commission know
And those stand to lose their license from them
Yeah
You can mean Kate with A board of you
So you're going to have a database of businesses
And, we are gonna check that data base
We'll get the list from people who all have any license
Then
That it fits in these categories
It will allow them
What I'm planning on us doing is sending and letter advising
All those people that will apply to letting them know
What we're doing, what they are amount is going
To be in minutes view
This isn't more work for you
Does this affect the tribal entities?
Yes because They have Abel licenses
I knew there was a law required
All of state laws
To apply it
Alco Hall on Indian Country
Just checking
The delay does have one effect
For instance, we are going to be using the combinator
Later this month
They would still require it under our current
Orrent coordinates
Because if you go into effect until July 1
To pay a $50 fee
That is our current
Occupational debt
Other than that
It should mean they're all
They wouldn't work your time
There's going to be a lot of money
I have the big meeting that day
Motion too
So for motion, don't worry about it
Motion 2 approved
15 other new business of any which is a residence
Supposing this agenda
16 staff report
17 mayor council committee
No, no
I got one
I'm your office shirt
The stain that is pointed out
That i didn't know there
And had put it on top so the bought
So they sold them to stay in
But
Girls were library
Outstanding jobs
There's nothing else
But
Man, They did not stand a job
It was great event
A herd of deposit from people in community
They were all in the middle
And they did it with limited resources
Which was even more
And what i got done
So I bought them for
What's a day
Did anybody see the
Mirror on Ryan's
Cleaners
Looks like
Kind of looks like a robot
Women
That was not interesting
Because they were finishing it up
Last night
And that's the time i talked about for a minute
I just had to ask more
It was a representative of the new
But he is
Man, you know
The guy who looked like a little boy
He would be his man and
His creation
You see
So
Woman
Man created
3AI
2 guys from Talsa
I think it was a
Cumes in Swalloway
And i
Think they called the birth of AI
Something similar to that
That's what i thought
It is very interesting
With all the dog of AI
And i know the girl that came to
The next one
But cat in a flower
She was from Dallas
Then they went on
First night's lunch, we got out of the
Girl from Austin
Couple guys up on the city
Pretty good variety
People
It had a coordination team
That had tents set up
They would have drinks and food
And stuff like that
But they were trying to explain
To me the different kinds of pates, cans
Nothing
Anyway
I think it was a good job
If you ever had chest go by look
We didn't
Have local artists
Just this
She painted the long corner of a library
Which would be south west corner
South West Corner
And one's like beach chair
That says my I'm a
In Route 66
Next to it is a swing
You can set on ledge
It looks like you're setting in chair
There was already a gentleman travel Route 66 from China
That's all ready set in the chair
And took yourself beyond his way through
So, kind of cool deal
Cool little selfie spot
We'll see how often it gets used
It will be on Facebook
I'm excited
You Will
You didn't sit in there
The German
I
You
We have more
Oh yeah
It's now called the MIPFA meeting for Monday
May 1st
For 3 minutes from April 2nd
So moved
So cool
Hi
Best of year, 2324 budget
I don't know if you want to talk about it or not
This is the MIPFA
Budget